Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
TYPHOON FAMILY
I've long dreamed of being a trader.
A trader who, even if not remarkable,
always fulfills her share of the work.
That has been my goal.
We've got so many here.
We should start sorting them out.
I've thought that was my dearest wish.
Oh, dear.
What is that smell?
What?
Oh, my! What do I do? Hold on.
No, this can't happen!
What do I do? But how?
How did a fire break out?
No, please.
Please stop.
No.
Oh, no.
SAMGOK WAREHOUSE
It's hot!
What do I do?
Please help!
This can't be happening.
What do I do?
Ms. Oh!
Darn it.
Oh Mi-seon!
Hold on. Hang in there.
Please…
Ms. Oh!
Now, before the dreams I once longed for,
regrets come to mind first.
I should've said goodbye
to my grandmother.
I should've told Mi-ho to quit her job
at the department store.
I should've bought
Beom's underwear sooner.
But what I regret the most now…
Oh Mi-seon!
Mi-seon!
…is that I never told him
how I actually feel about him.
I wish I had told him that I like him,
his gaze,
and everything about him.
I should've let him know.
Mi-seon.
Hang in there.
Oh Mi-seon!
It must've been so scary.
Let's get out of here.
EPISODE 13
LOVE BEYOND FEAR
ANJEONG HOSPITAL
That must be painful.
Just a minute, ma'am.
Could you check a patient here?
Ma'am, please.
Why isn't she getting any treatment?
She's had the tests already.
She's been waiting for ages.
Why aren't you treating her?
I told you the urgent test came back fine,
and the rest comes out tomorrow.
She'll be moved once she wakes.
But she inhaled
a mountain of jet-black smoke!
I bet she has.
Like I said,
please go get tested yourself.
What's going on? Ms. Oh.
Are you coming around?
Are you okay, Ms. Oh?
Ms. Oh.
Mi-seon!
Can you hear me, Mi-seon?
Open up your eyes!
-Hey, punk! Keep it down, will you?
-Mind the other patients, okay?
How inconsiderate.
Are you okay, Ms. Oh?
Mr. Kang.
What's up? Where does it hurt?
Go on, tell me.
I like you.
Come again?
I'm asking you to go out with me.
You're asking me that here?
Please, ma'am!
Please come take a look at him.
The bleeding won't stop!
Oh, no. Please take a look.
-Let me take a look.
-She's losing it.
I mean…
Come on, not in a place like this.
What about it?
It's safe and hygienic.
No way. I'll pretend I never heard that.
Let's do this again later.
What, again? Spare me the embarrassment.
No, I'm going to pretend I didn't hear it.
This just isn't right.
-Mr. Kang.
-Yeah?
What about our stock?
What happened to the gloves?
How is that the issue now?
Mr. Kang Tae-poong?
Hello, we're from the police department.
We'd like to ask you a few questions
regarding the fire.
Ms. Bun-i! Ma'am, wait for…
Wait up!
Slow down. Let me come with you!
Ma'am!
Where's my precious girl?
Over there.
-Are you okay, dear?
-Yes, Grandma.
I'm all good. Don't you worry.
-You're okay?
-Honestly, I'm okay.
Mom.
-Gosh, Tae-poong.
-Ms. Bun-i.
You rascal.
Look at the state of my baby girl.
How come you're unscathed?
Ma'am.
Ma'am, that wasn't exactly his fault…
Dear me. What if my beautiful bud
of a granddaughter had perished
without ever fully coming to bloom?
Could you have lived with that regret?
-I'm sorry, ma'am.
-I'm okay.
You foolish girl.
How did you get into such big trouble?
My old heart
has long hardened like a rock.
A piercing tragedy
might not do that big a damage.
But what about Mi-ho and Beom?
Did you consider how their tender hearts
will get shattered into pieces?
Grandma…
Your siblings aside,
have you thought about your life?
What about the life ahead of you?
Value and cherish yourself, okay?
I may have not given you
a comfortable life,
but that doesn't mean
you should knock yourself about.
My dear child.
-It must've been so hot in there.
-I'm all good.
-It must've been so suffocating and scary.
-I wasn't scared at all.
-Just how…
-I'm okay, Grandma.
-Don't worry, Grandma.
-You poor little thing.
Grandma, it's okay.
Don't cry.
You'll wear yourself out. It's all good.
I'm okay.
HOSPITAL
Here, ma'am.
I apologize for the harsh words earlier.
I shouldn't have blamed you at all.
No, ma'am.
It was my fault.
Can you make me a promise?
-I feel like I can ask you for a favor.
-Of course you can.
I noticed that my dear girl
has begun to smile again
after meeting you.
I mean, she's smiling again.
I'll fill her life with smiles.
All smiles and no tears.
Goodness, no. Make her cry.
Help her cry her eyes out
without holding back.
She's endured a lot at a young age.
Help her let go
of all the sorrows in her heart.
Can you do that for me?
Of course, I promise.
You can cry now too, ma'am.
We're a family now.
Get off. Didn't you hear me?
Unbelievable.
You've lost it, haven't you?
What have you done this time?
Did you ask about the delivery date
and the warehouse
to set the place on fire?
Did you torch the warehouse?
I haven't got time for this nonsense.
Listen, you crazy brat.
There was a person inside.
Mi-seon was there.
Did you do it on purpose?
So what?
Did Freckles die or something?
If she had died,
I'd be with the police, not you.
Oh, the police? Go ahead.
You've still got time to go see them.
But tell me.
Do you have any evidence?
I didn't do anything.
Listen up, lady.
You seem
to be having trouble grasping things,
but your job is to bring me
that promissory note or whatever.
Not my father, but me. Got it?
What's more, I suggest
you use your common sense.
Who do you think is next?
What a handsome kid.
STUDENT ID
PARK MIN-SEONG
Familiar, no?
Think about it.
The door was locked from the outside.
And yet, the warehouse burst into flames.
Are we sure it wasn't arson?
So, did you guys visit
Ms. Oh in the hospital?
Mr. Go here
had a total meltdown
at the sight of Ms. Oh in her sleep.
We got kicked out for being so loud.
So, is Ms. Oh going to be fine?
Fine, my foot.
She almost died.
She got first-degree burns
on her hands and arms.
She had some inhalation burn too,
but luckily she'll recover
after some rest.
-Hey.
-What's that?
-What's inside?
-It's just our goods from the warehouse.
Why bring them here?
-I have to go. I'm late.
-You're leaving?
-Jeez.
-Gosh.
I have a few more boxes in the car.
-That's enough, Mr. Kang.
-What?
They're all junk.
But why? They didn't get burned.
Take a look for yourself.
They still reek of smoke.
-What?
-These won't do.
They're for surgeries.
You can't use them.
Great effort, though.
I mean…
We know you did your best.
What are you even saying?
I can't believe my ears!
The deadline's a week away,
and now there's a problem?
Are you kidding me?
That's why we've come to ask
if you could extend
the deadline just by a few days.
There's no way!
You know all goods are to be collected
and shipped to Africa in one freighter!
My gosh, what an absolute nightmare!
You know what?
You're welcome to book a new ship
and take care of the delivery fees!
Look here.
It wasn't entirely due to
mismanagement on our part.
We had a fire.
"Look here"?
Ma'am, we had a fire.
Help your countrymen in need
before helping other nations.
There's no room for help here.
This is the protocol.
What about the damages for the delay?
Let's not argue over nothing.
Just go secure a new batch of products.
We're only here
because that's not so easy.
My goodness… Did you hear that, Mr. Jung?
This is why I don't want
small businesses getting involved.
How irresponsible!
When things go south, they just pretend
like it's none of their business.
In that case,
you could consider giving up your deal.
Then ten percent of the bid bond
will cover the damages--
Don't bring up giving up just yet.
You're taking the private sector's money,
corrupt bureaucrats.
Excuse me, don't make it sound
like we will get that money.
You'd be paying KOICA.
It's a different entity.
Then the right to the deal
will go to the runner-up bidder.
Does that mean it will go
to Pyo Merchant Marine?
-Yes.
-Goodness.
They're just as annoying.
You're like two seeds in a pod.
It's two peas in a pod!
Fine! "Two peas in a pod."
But that's not the key issue for me!
Just make sure
to deliver your goods on time!
Meet the deadline
and the quantity we agreed upon!
Our guests are leaving.
Validate their parking.
They only gave us 30 minutes.
She's not budging at all.
She wouldn't flinch for anything.
Let's talk to Blaze Eagles first.
Yes, we need that handled quickly.
Excuse me.
My goodness.
Ms. Jung.
Give me a few minutes.
Is it too rough for you?
Oh, no. I'm good.
This neighborhood
gives you quite the hike,
but the air here is so fresh.
It's not like any top-floor unit
of a high-rise complex.
I see.
Hello!
My gosh, it's so hot.
I may not have raised her like a princess.
Gosh, you scared me!
Still, it's admirable
how she seems to cherish others.
You mean the young lady?
It's rather pitiful.
Maybe it's because
she's used to walking on eggshells…
Well, I…
Ma'am.
Even so,
I'm sure she'll find someone
who'll recognize her warm heart's worth.
Please don't treat her poorly.
She may look feisty on the outside,
but she's a kind-hearted girl.
Ma'am, please don't misunderstand…
Her shoulders are squared,
and her tail is curled up beautifully.
Tail…
-She's got a tail?
-Sure.
Gosh, a dog! You scared me!
-My heart…
-Ms. Kim, you can wait in our bedroom…
My gosh. When did you come out, Ms. Bun-i?
-What's the matter?
-Oh, it's nothing.
-Ms. Jung!
-Hey, Beom.
I got 70!
My gosh.
You got 70 on the test?
See? I knew you had it in you!
You sweet thing.
You must be a genius.
What would you like to eat?
-Glazed sweet potato.
-Sweet potato?
I'll make it for you.
Let's get 90 on the next test.
Ninety points.
This is so exciting!
You got a whopping 70 points!
What did they say?
They can't produce more gloves
at the moment.
They can't produce gloves?
Because of recent bulk orders,
they're out of material.
Orders are flooding in,
but they don't have enough material.
It will take three months
until they can resume production.
We're facing bankruptcy here.
Don't even…
Please don't mention it, Myung-gwan.
Surely, the surgical gloves
can't be so hard to find.
Let's keep trying. We'll find a supplier.
Keep looking. We've got this.
-Come on, everyone.
-Okay.
Check for inventory
of the suppliers in the provinces.
Yes, okay.
HAEMONG FLOWER SHOP
Hi, you're here.
It must've been a long day.
It was rough, wasn't it?
Sorry I wasn't there for your discharge.
I don't mind it.
Thank you.
Should we have some dinner?
Let's eat.
-Thanks.
-You're an amazing cook, Ms. Bun-i.
It's just you're not much of a cook, dear.
Goodness.
Even water might taste better.
Remember, your father-in-law
likes his food well-seasoned.
But Tae-poong prefers
bland dishes over salty ones.
Drink enough water
if the dishes are too salty for you.
It tastes amazing.
Pretty lady, eat up.
-Always stay in good health.
-I will, Grandma.
I'm amazed you prepared
all my favorite dishes, Grandma.
Oh, sure.
What about me, Grandma?
Goodness, my baby.
You can have your fill too.
Wait.
We're short of one person.
Mi-ho is meeting her friends, Grandma.
YEOUIDO TOP PUB
STUDIO I LOVE YOU REUNION
AT YEOUIDO TOP PUB
Bang!
-Down a shot!
-Let's begin again.
-Zero.
-Seven.
-Bang!
Hey, you got it wrong!
Wait, no!
This time, it's soju.
-Down a shot!
-Cheers.
Hey, we've got another pitcher of beer.
Gosh, we're getting beer non-stop.
We can't leave your glass empty, Mr. Jung.
-Drink up.
-Oh, dear.
Look, I've got some soju.
Gosh.
Let me refill your glasses, ladies.
Why aren't you guys drinking?
Is Tae-poong skipping again?
I thought he promised to come this time.
Why do we always get
either Kim Chu-seok or him?
-Hey, Man No. 4.
-Yes?
Where's Tae-poong?
You said you called him.
Tae-poong didn't recognize me.
What about him?
Ha Cheong-il impersonator.
-Oh, Wang Nam-i?
-Nam-i or whatever.
He sang Park Nam-jung's song,
not Ha Cheong-il's.
His name is Wang Nam-mo, not Wang Nam-i.
-Sure, Nam-mo.
-Nam-mo.
-We know that.
-Of course.
-Don't get it wrong.
-Okay.
-Cheers, everyone!
-Cheers!
-Let's drink up, okay?
-Jeez, she's wasted.
-Mi-ho sure is.
Can we get more soju, ma'am?
-We're good, ma'am.
-We have some here.
Mi-ho's running late tonight.
-What is that?
-This?
Do you want to try it?
Ms. Bun-i, they produced this serum
using the technology they developed
while carrying out research on diabetes.
It keeps your skin healthy.
Even the bottle
is designed quite elegantly.
I love it.
If I get prettier than this,
the young men in the area will badger me
for giving them butterflies!
You needn't worry about that.
Ms. Oh. Come here and try this.
-Little Ms. Oh got me this, and I love it.
-Really?
It's pretty unique.
-Right?
-For sure.
Let's keep your skin nice and moist.
-Can I step outside for a bit?
-Okay.
Where are you going? Seeing someone?
Goodness, no.
I'm going out for a stroll.
I'll be back soon.
-See you.
-Okay.
-Are you sure you should be out here?
-Yeah.
I had a big meal,
so a walk will help me digest.
It felt rather stuffy inside too.
How does it feel
to see the person you like?
I thought you'd pretend
you never heard it.
I love it.
That I get to see you like this.
It was really rough today, wasn't it?
I felt
somewhat lost.
But I'm good now.
I'm really fine.
I'm sorry.
If only I had noticed the fire sooner.
Don't say that.
It was my fault.
From now on, I will never leave you alone.
You know…
Mi-seon, you are…
The one you really like?
No.
The one I love.
Hello?
Man No. 2. Please come over quickly.
What?
Come on. They gave me a twister shot!
A shot of that can take even bulls down.
-Jeez.
-I honestly want to quit drinking…
-Mi-ho!
-Just a bit further.
Who the hell are you?
It's not…
Well… You know…
Are you okay, Mi-ho?
-Why did you get so wasted?
-Hey, that's mine.
It's not what you think.
Hello, Man No. 2. I'm Man No. 4.
Abracadabra.
-Oh, right. Hello.
-Hi.
Why didn't you come
to the Studio I Love You reunion?
Chu-seok said he left both you
and Tae-poong countless pager messages.
He kept inviting us to a group date
with women from other cohorts.
What? When did he ever do that?
What, a group date?
Have you finally lost your mind?
You don't get to say that
in your state, Mi-ho.
What have I done so wrong?
Go on and tell me. What's my problem?
Your sister was just discharged today.
Why were you at the party?
-Are you an alcoholic or what?
-I drank because I was upset!
What's wrong with it?
Do you not approve of a girl drinking?
It becomes an issue if you can't hold
your liquor, regardless of your gender.
Don't you know
how unsafe the world has gotten?
Don't give me a lecture!
Who do you think you are?
-Who are you to say that?
-What?
Hey, do you really have to ask?
Why are you even dating me, Mi-ho?
Are you dating me out of pity
because I kept following you around?
No.
Because you were annoying.
It was because you were annoying
and I was bored.
I'll go grab a taxi. Wait here.
Take this with you, Nam-mo!
I didn't get the fruit basket for you.
It's for your sister.
Take it home with you.
I started seeing you
because you were annoying.
That's how it was at the start!
But I've fallen for you.
I'll still like you
even when your situation worsens.
What can I do when I still care for you
even after all the humiliation?
Jeez, I can't stand this stupid melodrama!
Mom…
Get over here, Nam-mo.
Mom, are you drunk?
Come on!
Life will get really tiring
if you start squabbling so soon.
If you're not taking this home,
I'll take it--
No, ma'am. I'm going to eat everything.
Really?
Good. Come here, Nam-mo.
Carry it for her.
Why don't we
cure our hangover?
Let's go. Come inside.
That hits the spot.
Gumiho.
Wait, I meant… Mi-ho.
For what it's worth,
Nam-mo makes amazing ramyeon, doesn't he?
Here's your kimchi.
-I hope you haven't nagged at Mi-ho again.
-Of course, I didn't!
Have some kimchi with your ramyeon.
To think I gave birth to this brat
and kept him under my roof for decades…
How unfortunate of me.
You don't even like kimchi, Mom.
What do you mean? I love it.
Eat up.
My mom never gives the egg yolk
to anyone, not even me.
I gave it to you plenty of times.
You're so annoying. Hurry and eat up.
Could we get the gloves custom-made?
It's a bulk order.
Oh, I see.
So the latex needs to be imported?
Okay, I understand.
Wasting breath on the obvious.
Why do you keep bringing up rubber gloves?
Should surgeons wear
the dish-washing gloves?
Do you think surgical operations
are the same as making kimchi?
I'm hanging up! You're wasting my time.
They won't even answer. Darn it.
The manufacturer client list was here.
What on earth?
It's a mess.
Did you go through the documents here?
No, the cabinets here are in the shade.
That's bad feng shui.
I swear I had these arranged neatly.
IMPORT DECLARATION CERTIFICATES
CLIENT TRANSACTION INVOICE
-Hey.
-Min-seong.
So you're Min-seong.
-Get a snack with your buddy.
-Min-seong!
What are you doing here?
Go to the study room now.
-This guy came up to me--
-Don't mind him.
This gentleman here is my colleague.
I forgot to bring your meal today.
Get something with your friends.
No, ask the study room owner
to order you jjajangmyeon.
Get going. Come on.
Off you go.
STUDY ROOM
Why are you back again?
What's the matter with you lot?
Your son doesn't take after you.
He won't take my money.
I bet you scared him
by forcing him to go upstairs.
Next time,
I'll be taking him.
How many boxes do we have?
It'll take more than a year
to sell them all in the domestic market!
I'll look into wholesale dealers quickly.
Your son had a plan this time--
How could you place an order
on a bid you hadn't even won?
Have you lost your senses?
This time, we had the deal
almost in the bag--
"Almost"?
"Almost"!
Have Hyun-jun come quickly
and check the inventory.
-Snap to it!
-Yes, sir.
Aren't you a professional?
Why are you holding back?
Is it because you are broke?
Knock me down,
and I'll pay you, you broke bum!
Take that.
Jeez!
Gosh.
What was that for?
You crazy bastard…
Darn it!
Today's your unlucky day.
I had a really bad day, you know.
Look at me.
You worthless scum!
Hyun-jun! Hey, knock it off!
Hey, stop it!
-Let me go!
-Enough!
You broke bastard!
GYEONGIL MEDICAL SUPPLIES
Hello, I'm with Typhoon Trading.
-Hi.
-Do you perhaps have surgical gloves
powdered with corn starch
instead of talcum powder?
We only stock ones with talcum powder.
-Really?
-Yes.
We don't have three million pairs.
Right? Thank you for your time.
I heard there was
a major incident of late.
-Pardon?
-About the surgical gloves.
Everyone's in a frenzy.
I've got it.
-What on… Hey, are you okay?
-Ms. Oh.
-Wait.
-Take a seat.
-Slow down.
-I figured it out.
What do you mean?
I know why Blaze Eagles
is short on supplies.
Have you looked
into what I asked, Mr. Bae?
Yes, I talked to the factory manager
in Malaysia just as you asked.
One company placed an order
with Blaze Eagles two weeks ago
for three million pairs.
For three million? Doesn't that
match the quantity of our order?
-It's a Korean company too.
-A Korean company?
-Can it be--
-Yes, it's Pyo Merchant Marine.
I've talked to all the wholesalers
dealing in medical supplies.
There's a rumor that Pyo Merchant Marine
is seeking a wholesaler
to take their bulk supply
of surgical gloves.
Everyone is worried the large inventory
will cause prices to drop.
They've lost their minds.
They proceeded with the order
even when they had lost the bid?
Turns out they have what we want.
-What now? Don't tell me you're going.
-Mr. Kang.
-No, wait.
-You shouldn't go see them.
They'd never give us their stock.
It will be like
banging your head against a wall.
You know how ruthless they are.
Mr. Kang, you know
it will be a waste of time.
No.
At least I'll be able to see it myself.
Mr. Kang.
What are you up to?
Why sneak in like some common thief
and take a peek at our goods
without permission?
I thought you're here to see me.
Did you order these?
-Who will you sell these to?
-Jeez, you stress me out.
That's all you've got to ask
after coming all the way here?
By any chance,
did you set our warehouse on fire?
-To get the deal instead?
-What, me?
Do you think I can't sell this junk?
I got it wrong, right?
You may not be in your right mind,
but you were never such a lowlife, right?
Thanks for your kind words, punk.
Can you get out of my sight now?
I'm having a really bad day today.
If that's not the case…
I'm saying,
if you didn't
set the fire…
let me borrow these gloves.
-Come again?
-Or sell them to me.
I may not be able to pay you right away.
-But I'll add a handsome interest--
-Wake up, you clown.
Are you that desperate?
Yeah.
I'm really desperate.
If that's the case, Tae-poong,
show me how much you want them.
I might consider it then.
Look, you're not going to have any luck
when you're standing tall.
Come on.
Lower your head humbly. There you go.
That's more like it!
That's what I'm talking about.
Tell me everything you want.
All I want in return are these gloves.
What do I want?
Nothing, you idiot.
I'd rather burn them
than give them to you.
I know they catch fire easily too.
Hyun-jun!
I…
I was wrong.
I will…
I apologize for everything.
So,
please…
help me out here.
Otherwise, my company won't survive.
Please do me a favor.
That was my goal in the first place.
To make you go bankrupt.
Even the back of your head
rubs me the wrong way.
TOJONG SUNDAE SOUP
I thought soju would taste sweet
on a day like this.
It's just as bitter.
I wonder why you loved
this bitter thing so much.
MAKGEOLLI, SUNDAE SOUP
I should've joined you
for a drink back then.
I should've poured you a glass at least.
I never got to do this for you
when it was this easy.
I thought you'd wait for me.
That breaks my heart the most.
What about you, Dad?
What upset you so much that night?
Welcome.
-Can we get one more glass, ma'am?
-Sure.
Don't pour your own drink.
You'll bring your father bad luck.
I'm here too, Mr. Kang.
You're clueless
about the drinking etiquette.
How did you know
I was saving a spot for my dad?
I just do, punk.
Drink up.
Hey, Tae-poong.
A bizarre thing happened to me.
What kind of bizarre thing?
Back when I was sleeping at your office
after arguing with my mom,
that lady paid a visit
in the dead of night.
You know, the lady
who used to work for your company.
I swear I had these arranged neatly.
Ms. Cha, did you reorganize
the files in this office?
I took a look yesterday
and noticed how they were arranged
by date from right to left.
I know that's how you arrange files.
So, he would never rip out a page
even if he made errors.
DATA ENTRY ERROR, NEXT PAGE
Why is this page gone?
AUGUST 17TH
TYPHOON TRADING
MOMO'S PUB
Darn it.
Why do those bastards
keep insisting it's here?
What can it be
that they're throwing this hissy fit?
What are you doing, Ms. Cha?
What exactly are you doing?
Why is everyone out to get me?
Why won't any of you just leave me alone?
Ms. Cha!
I bet it was you.
You hid it, didn't you?
You knew everything
and hid it on purpose, didn't you?
What do you mean?
What is it that I supposedly hid?
You know what.
Without it, my son will be in big trouble.
What are you talking about?
I won't know unless you tell me.
You know, the promissory note.
Promissory note?
The proof that Pyo Bak-ho borrowed money.
Are you working under his orders?
You really have no idea.
Oh, no. It's truly missing.
What do I do?
-What's this promissory note?
-What am I to do?
Talk to me.
Why the hell do you need it?
You already saw that the ledger
was missing a page!
-The loan must've been on there.
-So why are you looking for the note?
Did he perhaps
bribe you?
Did he?
You're right.
He offered me money, and I took it.
When your father's funeral was being held…
While his body was in the funeral home,
I accepted a bribe.
A huge one, at that.
My hand instinctively reached out
and wouldn't let go of that money.
I had no other choice, okay?
My wage was withheld,
my husband is a total money pit,
and I couldn't pay my son's tutors!
I needed money to keep my family afloat!
So what?
What about the others?
Didn't you ever think of them?
You're really clueless, aren't you?
Even if I hadn't complied,
Pyo Merchant Marine might've found it,
perhaps through a harsher way.
Don't you agree? Let's be real.
If they meant to pay,
they would've done it ages ago.
-They were never going to pay it back.
-So what?
"So what"?
If I were you, Mr. Kang,
I'd give it to them and get it over with.
Think about how much we suffered
over that note.
We're about to go bankrupt,
and Ms. Oh got hurt.
Who knows what will happen next?
So let's find that note
and give it to them.
-Come on.
-Listen, Ms. Cha!
Don't you feel bad for my father?
Seriously, how could you do this to us?
Snap out of it, Kang Tae-poong!
Why dwell on the dead man?
The living must go on!
What in the world…
MOMO'S PUB
TYPHOON TRADING
CEO KANG TAE-POONG
Tae-poong will…
do a good job.
"He'll do a good job."
That's what he said.
He said you'd do a good job.
TYPHOON TRADING
MOMO'S PUB
Mr. Kang…
Ms. Oh.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but could you place
an order for this again?
TYPHOON TRADING
CEO KANG TAE-POONG
I think it reflects poorly…
on the company, not on myself.
Please take care of it.
Where are you going?
To do my job.
What kind of a jerk
parks their car this way?
They didn't even leave their number.
At least you're consistently ill-mannered,
I'll give you that.
You know Ms. Cha Seon-taek, don't you?
"Cha Seon-taek"?
What, as in tea selection?
You won't be seeing her again
because I found out everything.
I don't follow.
By any chance…
did my father come to you…
to ask for help?
What a strange thing to say.
How could I have met Mr. Kang
when he's long gone?
Look closely.
Mr. Kang is right here.
You've lost your mind.
What's wrong?
Do you feel anxious?
Sure, your father was just as anxious.
Watching your company go bankrupt
must make your stomach churn.
Even if it kills me,
Typhoon Trading will never go down.
Why else would a trading company's owner
visit you if not to strike a deal?
-A deal?
-You have surgical gloves.
Sell them to me.
What?
I hope you'll give me a discount.
I suffered a huge loss, you see.
I thought you had
a good head on your shoulders.
-Turns out it was all a bluff.
-Why won't you sell them to me?
I bet you're losing sleep
over what to do with them.
That's none of your concern.
Here's the most important issue.
Do you have money?
I'm asking if you can pay for the gloves.
-You're asking me about money?
-That's right.
Given our history,
you can't be considering buying on credit.
I do have it.
The money, that is.
You took money from my father.
Shouldn't that be enough to cover it?
-What?
-Haven't you heard?
I'm talking about your promissory note.
It seems you haven't heard
that I recovered it.
"Promissory note"?
I can't recall if such a thing existed.
The money from nine years ago
should now be…
What with the interest… No.
Throw in all the overdue interest,
and this office
and the building should be mine.
Watch your darn mouth, you little brat.
Don't you worry.
I couldn't care less about your building.
Then what?
I want the three million pairs
of gloves in your storage.
What?
I'm losing out big time, aren't I?
What's the matter?
Do you think I don't have it?
That may be the case.
SEOUL OFFICE OF PUBLIC PROCUREMENT SERVICE
Why is this young man here?
Did I call him over?
-No.
-What perfect timing.
-We've been talking about our deal.
-Deal? What deal?
Do you think your company
can deliver the goods on time?
Try it if you can.
We can deliver our goods even today.
Deals aren't some children's game.
We have time until the deadline.
Respect the protocol.
To put it bluntly,
Typhoon Trading hasn't messed up yet.
Exactly. Oh, my gosh.
Hey, you're being nice to us
all of a sudden.
As if! What brings you here anyway?
-It's just--
-We want to ask for a deadline extension.
-You shouldn't have led with that.
-Why not?
Mistakes happen. We're only humans.
Haven't you been listening?
-I'm giving up now.
-My goodness.
Take my gut and do what you want.
Tell him he can take my gut.
He says to open up his stomach.
Who is sick? I'm a doctor.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hey, Ms. Oh. What's up?
What?
Pick up the pace,
and we can all wrap up quickly.
Speed it up even more,
and we'll be out in no time.
Hey, watch your step.
Don't you dare touch them!
You bastards.
So, did you come
looking for a fight, Tae-poong?
Bring it on. Come at me, you punk.
Jerk.
Ms. Oh.
Are you out of your mind?
You did it, didn't you?
LOVE BEYOND FEAR
TYPHOON FAMILY
You better have it
if you want to save that petty position
your father left behind.
Will an apology change anything?
My father will hear it too.
And you'll hear it too.
I have to find it quickly.
I was feeling rushed
and I'm running out of time.
You can go with Honey Poong
or Baby Poong, something like that.
Why don't we take a day trip
to the sea with Beom?
Tae-poong, that kid,
knows about the promissory note,
but he doesn't have it.
Don't you want to know
why I need those gloves?
But I never beg.
I make others beg.
Subtitle translation by: Jeongwoo Kim